(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-29T13:13:54.353936",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Hi, how are you?
Are you calling up my phone?
Baby, tell me what is wrong
Don't you ever let me go
Hi, I am good.
I am still looking for proof
Am I good enough for you?
Don't you tell me what's my rule
This is me, are you coming on the ride?
We're going super high
Got to be who, what I like
You & me, are you ready for the fight?
Alright, alright, alright
Stronger than I ever been before
This is who I am
Nothing in the way
Today and far away
One, two, three, go!
Hi, how are you?
Are you calling up my phone?
Baby, tell me what is wrong
Don't you ever let me go
Hi, I am good
I am still looking for proof
Am I good enough for you?
Don't you tell me what's my rule
This is me, are you coming on the ride?
We're going super high
Got to be who what I like
You and me, are you ready for the fight?
Alright, alright, alright
Stronger than I ever been before
This is who I am
Nothing in the way
Today and far away
You and me
We make the part of me
I give you my big red heart
My, my big red heart
I'll be true to my red heart
Hi, over there
Thank you for coming along
On this journey of my own
Promise me you won't let go
Yes, this is me
I am falling, but I'm strong
'Cause you got me in your arms
Don't you ever let me go
I want you to come with me on the ride
This is going super high
I am falling from the sky
Got to be who you wanna be, that's right
Alright, alright, alright, let's go
I am still a girl
Figuring out what's true or false in this whole wide world
I'm your only girl
Tell me once more what's really going on with you
I'm looking for the right one on the road
The one that'll always take me back to you
This can be my home, will you be my home?
Stronger than I ever been before
This is who I am
Nothing in the way
Today and far away
You and me
We make the part of me
I give you my big red heart
My, my big red heart
I'll be true to my red heart
Nothing in the way
Today and far away
You and me
We make the part of me
I give you my big red heart
My, my big red heart
I'll be true to my red heart
We love Haachama!
We'll continue putting all our hearts into everything!
Thank you for singing RED HEART!
I give all of you guys my big RED HEART from Haachama!
Thank you so much, Ruffians, for coming to Hololive 3rd Anniversary Live!
Thanks to Hololive!
Hololive 3rd Anniversary Live!
Thanks to Hololive for coming here, really arigato!
Today, our entire concert is to share our love and appreciation for Hololive!
I stand by, Zenmates, Kouhai, and you, Ruffians!
And this trip is going to be tough with all the Hololive Ruffians!
Get ready, okay?
And of course, if you do want to know, our hashtag right now, Ruffians...
Our hashtag for today is #FuwamocoFeed!
Please take lots of screenshots, pishaw pishaw!
And tweet about us on SNS, okay?
So hashtag is #FuwamocoFeed, screenshots are lots of SNS, and post it, okay?
Yeah, pochito, right?
Take a look and go, "Oh!" Pochito, what you doing?
But our very first song that we performed with Haachama is RED HEART!
It's a very precious song of ours, and you know, it's because of Haachama senpai that actually...
Fuwamoco, we found Hololive because of Haachama senpai, and to be able to meet Hololive, it's very, very important for us!
We love you so much, Hololive!
We're waiting for you to go out again, okay? So Haachama senpai, daisuki dayo!
もっとよ！ もっとよ！
More! More!
もっとよ！
More!
We designed today's stage
with a very special Hololive feeling in mind, right?
そう、今回のステージはホロライブをテーマに作ってもらいました！
That's right, this stage was made with Hololive as the theme!
やー！ぱっぱ！
Yay! Pappa!
And we really hope that the love for Hololive will reach you today!
Yeah, we'll be singing and dancing, of course!
With some very special surprise vibes,
so please look forward to it!
And, oh! There might be a big announcement, too!
Yay!
重大発表もあるから離さず
There'll be major announcements too, so
最後まで見てください！
please keep watching until the very end!
Please watch to the very end!
Okay? Stay tuned, yay!
High-five!
What a mystic for the world!
And all of Advent came to celebrate!
Thank you!
Yeah, but you know,
we just celebrated our third anniversary with a live a few weeks ago!
Yeah! It was such a fun time, but now we're in our fourth year!
What is now? What is scandal?
Happy third anniversary!
It's been really nuts if you think about it, because we've had the evolution of getting to know each other from the very first HoloLive game
to now. Series later, we gift each other little silly gifts, gnomes, a little cute plushie, bookmark, and I just really appreciate being everyone's friend.
Let's be friends for many more years to come!
Well, of course, it's FuwaMoco day, so obviously talking about you, but to keep in mind, I do feel this way about all of Advent, but it's applicable to everybody personal.
You know, since we all got together, it's just been so clear that all of us were meant to be friends, you know what I mean? I truly can't imagine being in a gen with more hardworking and amazing people than you guys, and every day I'm just so, so grateful to be able to have you guys here as my friends and as my genmates, I'm so happy!
三周年おめでとうございます！
Congratulations on your 3rd anniversary!
All right, let me hold your paws, Licerissa. All right.
三周年おめでとうございます！
Congratulations on your 3rd anniversary!
You know, we've been through so much together as Advent with you guys. You know, like you fed us boss, you got us muskets, you made sure I didn't die, you helped me hazard across the street, and I couldn't imagine starting this journey with anybody else other than you guys. So I'm so happy we're here celebrating together!
You know, but our concert has only just started, right?
We get to sing together with Hololive, you know? Well, FuwaMoco, we wanted to sing a song that means so much to us. You know, without our side-by-side hard work, we wouldn't be here, you know?
And when we all debuted, there was FuwaMoco, and we're just about to celebrate their third anniversary. So, with all the love and respect in our hearts, please listen to this very special version of Hololive English Myth's original song.
Reunion!
Sing out boldly again,
continuing this odyssey.
We'll start this new refrain brimming with memories!
And when the clouded skies become bright, let's reunite!
Ready? Set? Stream!
It's showtime, baby!
...I would say.
Today's broadcast on slight delay...
Rubbing out the scuff,
is it really enough? stuck on buffering endlessly, why?!
Take it easy, what have we learned?
Start a fire in their hearts when the PC burns!
Uh... optimistic?
Focus on a quick fix!
Teach new dogs all of our old tricks!
Still going stronger than ever, and never saying die (Whoo!)
And I'm aware it's ironic, but where's the freaking lie?
Dreamers to streamers to entertainers to senpai!!
"I'm not losing to you young people!!"
Ignore her, it's a mid-death crisis.
"Gura!!!!!!"
Spanning new dimensions, we can bring another mystery to light!
Planning our ascension, dancing in flight, we ignite...
Through this world and beyond, our distant dreams have brought us here.
A strong, unyielding bond, guiding us endlessly, will bring us moments that we hold dear.
Time rushes on; and though these winds may scatter us,
we'll keep this promise: when the moment's finally right, we'll always find a way to reunite!
I'm diving in again, now it's time to sink or swim!
Let's try the deeper end, but could you hold my fin?
Vibing with everyone, let's kick back and ponder puns!
Tako time anytime, let's get cozy and have fun! (Wah!)
Nobody escapes death!!
And I know that it's morbid, years come and go
I'll still pretend I've got this killing thing sorted, listen.
I wanna look cool, but I keep on tripping and falling,
guess I'll keep playing the fool 'til— hold up, nakama are calling, yatta~!
Countless moments led us to this day: triumph and sorrow, hope for tomorrow— we'll always find our way, come what may!
In every universe, we were always meant to meet.
I'll lead a boundless search. We will never know defeat!
My wings will guide your hands as the fateful days go by,
we will cut a path through a never-ending sky!
Drawing us together, I can sense another wish is coming true.
We'll be friends fur-ever, loyal and true, me and you!
Sing out again! The clouded skies give way to clear;
we'll start this new refrain brimming with memories! Another story's starting right here...
We'll keep forging ahead to make a saga all our own
whichever paths we tread, steadily journeying, we know we're never really alone—
if we believe wherever fate may find us, our love will bind us,
every epic chapter we write will set us on the path to reunite!
目覚まし時計は鳴り止まないような
時計の針は止まらない この歌を思い出して
もし失敗したっていいよ
Even if you fail, it's okay,
あの優しい声がそばにいたから
Because that gentle voice was right by my side.
恋に傷ついて 道に迷った日もあったけれど
Though there were days I was hurt by love and lost my way,
いつだって探してたのさ 輝けるはずの
I was always searching for what should shine—
Birthday
my birthday.
Everyday 解き放て 躊躇いがちなそのエモーション
Everyday, set free that hesitant emotion,
時代のせいにしたってつまらないよ
Blaming the times is so boring.
Everyday 君であれ 立ち止まることもあるけれど
Everyday, just be yourself, even if you stop sometimes,
ねえ きっと君は大丈夫
Hey, I'm sure you'll be fine.
Step and Go!!
誰もの記憶の中に
Within everyone's memories
ある大切なあの笑顔を 抱き締めてる
Is that precious smile, holding it close.
いつか君にまた会いたい
I want to see you again someday,
なら 素直にちゃんと 気持ち伝えたい
So I want to honestly and properly convey my feelings.
自分自身で引いたボーダーラインなら さあ飛び越えて
If you've drawn a border line yourself, come on, jump right over it!
いつだって描いていこう 君らしい色で
Let's always picture it in your own unique colors.
Birthday
Everyday 煌めいて 今動き出したエモーション
Everyday, sparkling, the emotion that just started moving,
誰かのせいにしたってつまらないよ
Blaming someone else is so boring.
Everyday らしくあれ やがてこの雨も上がって
Everyday, act naturally, soon this rain will clear up,
ねえ きっと君は大丈夫
Hey, I'm sure you'll be fine.
Step and Go!!
どんな時だって 涙は出るけれど
No matter when, tears will fall, but
止まない雨はないように 君ならできるよ
Just as there's no rain that never stops, you can do it!
Step and Go!!
Everyday 解き放て 躊躇いがちなそのエモーション
Everyday, set free that hesitant emotion,
時代のせいにしたってつまらないよ
Blaming the times is so boring.
Everyday 君であれ 立ち止まることもあるけれど
Everyday, just be yourself, even if you stop sometimes,
ねえ きっと君は大丈夫
Hey, I'm sure you'll be fine.
Step and Go!!
FUWAMOCOの居場所であるhololiveを作ってくれてありがとう
Thank you for creating hololive, the place where FUWAMOCO belongs!
でりー~だいりー~!
Deili~ Dayi~!
届けちゃおう
Let's deliver it!
全力実況中 挑戦配信中
Full-effort live streaming, challenge streaming!
ほらね 楽しいは 発見
Look, fun is a discovery!
また新しい隙間が見つかったよ
We found another new gap!
(てりー~だいりー~) ちょっぴり乗る
(Deili~ Dayi~!) Catching the vibe a little,
近所にできたカフェのケーキ
The cake from the new cafe in the neighborhood
なんかすごく美味しかったんだよ
Was somehow super delicious!
腹ペコになりなよ 小さい頃食べたことない？
Be hungry! Haven't you eaten something like this since you were little?
新曲ちょっと気になっちゃって お出しちゃおう
A new song got me a little curious, so let's put it out!
なあなあ ともだち いっしょに遊ぼう
Hey hey friend, let's play together!
でいり〜だいあり〜！
Daily Diary!
届けちゃおう！
Let's deliver it!
せ〜しゅん 実況中！ ちょ〜せん 配信中！
Youth streaming! Challenge broadcasting!
ほらね、 楽しい を 発見！
Look, I found some fun!
また 新しい 『 好き 』 が 見つかった よ
I found a new "favorite" once again!
近所 に できた カフェ の 『 ケーキ 』
The "cake" at the cafe in the neighborhood
なんか すごく 美味しかっ た ん だ よ
Was somehow super delicious!
知ら なかった ゲーム や 聴いた こと ない 歌
Games I didn't know or songs I've never heard,
ちょっと 気 に なったら 手 を 出し ちゃう
If I'm a bit curious, I'll reach right out!
ほ ・ ら ・ ま ・ た いっしょに遊ぼう ！
Hey, come on, let's play together!
10 連 ガチャ 引い て みよう
Let's try pulling a 10-roll gacha!
ホラーゲーム やってみよう
Let's try playing a horror game!
あの 曲 歌ってみよう
Let's try singing that song!
ぜんぶ が 、 もう 楽しい の ！
Everything is already so much fun!
窓 の 向こう の 笑顔 に 手 を 振っ ちゃう ！
Wave your hand to the smile on the other side of the window!
アニメ 視聴 中 … 発見 ！
Watching anime... Found it!
モブ の キャラ に 推せる ポテンシャル
A mob character with serious potential!
知名度 ない マンガ や 思いつい た 新 ネタ
An obscure manga or a brand new idea!
あたん ない 天気 予報 も きっと 面白い こと に なる ん だ よ
Even an inaccurate weather forecast will surely turn out interesting!
すっごく 楽しく て 寝付け なかっ た ん だ ！
It was so much fun I couldn't fall asleep!
特別 すごい こと なんて 、 そう おこらない 現実
Nothing particularly amazing happens in reality,
だけど 、 その エッセンス
But with that essence,
仮想 の 世界 、 夢 に 変えて 毎日 が パラダイス ！
Turning the virtual world into a dream makes every day a paradise!
おもいっきり 遊ん で 笑っ ちゃおう ！
Let's play to our heart's content and laugh!
どんな 毎日 も 楽しく なっ ちゃう ん だ
Every single day becomes so much fun!
だって 、 いつだって ほら あなた が 待っ てる の ！
Because you're always waiting there, look!
みんなで 毎日 を 出会え た 嬉しい を
The joy of meeting every day together with everyone,
みんな と 一緒に 気分 は ね 、 もう 最高潮 ！
Together with everyone, our mood is at its peak!
窓 の 向こう の 笑顔 に 手 を 振っ て
Waving to the smile on the other side of the window,
配信 で とどける our daily diary
Delivering our daily diary through streaming!
せ〜しゅん 実況中！ ちょ〜せん 配信中！
Youth streaming! Challenge broadcasting!
でいり〜だいあり〜！
Daily Diary!
届けよう！
Let's deliver it!
全米を落とす覚悟してきた！
We came prepared to conquer the whole US!
何それ！
What's that?!
勝てる気がしないんだけど！
I don't feel like we can win at all!
あきらめたら実況終了だよ！
If you give up, the stream is over!
え、待って、終わりたくない！
Huh, wait, I don't want it to end!
どんな 毎日 も 楽しく なっ ちゃう ん だ
Every single day becomes so much fun!
だって 、 いつだって ほら あなた が 待っ てる の ！
Because you're always waiting there, look!
みんなで 毎日 を 出会え た 嬉しい を
The joy of meeting every day together with everyone,
みんな と 一緒に 気分 は ね 、 もう 最高潮 ！
Together with everyone, our mood is at its peak!
窓 の 向こう の 笑顔 に 手 を 振っ て
Waving to the smile on the other side of the window,
配信 で とどける our daily diary
Delivering our daily diary through streaming!
せ〜しゅん 実況中！ ちょ〜せん 配信中！
Youth streaming! Challenge broadcasting!
でいり〜だいあり〜 届けよう！
Daily Diary, let's deliver it!
みんな大〜すきだよー！！ 3年間分のDaily Diaryをみんなと一緒に作り上げられたのは最高の宝物
We love you all so much!! Building 3 years of Daily Diaries together with everyone is our greatest treasure!
Aw! And that was "Daily Diary"! Woo!
We're really happy to perform it together with Miko-chi senpai, Korone senpai, and Watame senpai! Yay!
But the reason why we chose "Daily Diary", it's because "Daily Diary" is a really special song to us.
We listened to it lots and lots before we debuted, and we just really wanted to start creating our own "Daily Diary" together with you mortals.
Yeah, so we listened to it over and over, and we kept on imagining what that might look like.
Yeah, so for Fuwamoco in particular, "Daily Diary" is a really important song that we listened to a lot before our debut.
Yeah, and the feeling from back then, we still remember it so well, and we really wanted to debut and create "Daily Diary" with everyone.
Yeah, we had no choice, but in these 3 years, the memories we created with everyone turned into an even more wonderful "Daily Diary" than we could have ever imagined, you know?
Thank you all for your support! We've made it even more wonderful with you mortals!
But, I think we still have a lot more coming up!
Including one more gacha! A super-duper big announcement! It's really important, okay?
Don't forget that! So make sure you stay with us until the very end, okay?
But we still have some very special songs like this for you!
I'm a little nervous. (Me too!)
So let's get ready then! Let's get going!
Okay! Here we go!
「キミのヒロインは誰…？」
“Who will be your heroine...?”
おぼえてる優しい
I still remember your gentle words
キミの言葉にキュンとして
that made my heart skip a beat.
上手に言えない
Unable to say it well,
代わりに笑いかけてみたの
I tried smiling at you instead.
目が合った気がした
I felt like our eyes met,
それだけで
and just that
鼓動はハネた
made my heartbeat race.
お願い
Please,
勘違いじゃありませんように
I hope I'm not just imagining things.
そっと心の中で
Softly in my heart,
熱い視線送った
I sent you a passionate gaze.
振り向いてって願っちゃってた
I kept wishing you would turn around.
ヒロインオーディション
Heroine audition—
エントリーしたらワタシ
once I enter, I wonder...
「ねぇ、選んでくれるかな…？」
“Hey, will you choose me...?”
マジメな性格
Such a serious personality—
おはようだけで伝わるよ
just 'good morning' says it all.
何気ないつぶやき
That casual murmuring
もしかしてと期待してる
makes me hope 'maybe...?'
眩しい素敵な人ばかりで
Everyone around is so dazzling and wonderful,
自信もなくて
and I lack confidence,
それでも本音では
but even so, deep down,
365日
365 days a year
もっと近づきたい
I want to get closer.
ワタシなりのペースになるけど
It'll be at my own pace, but—
ヒロインオーディション
Heroine audition—
勇気をだしたらキミは
if I gather my courage, will you
「ねぇ、答えてくれるかな…？」
“Hey, give me an answer...?”
出会った瞬間ってかなり
The moment we met was quite
すごいミラクル
an amazing miracle.
このチャンスは赤い糸
This chance is a red thread of fate;
ギュッと手繰り寄せて
pulling it in tight,
運命にしよう
let's make it our destiny.
信じて…
Believing...
まっすぐ…
Straight ahead...
せーので言葉にして…！
Putting it into words on three...!
「キミのヒロインは誰…？」
“Who will be your heroine...?”
きっとキミの心を
I'm sure I'll make your heart
動かしてみせるよ
move and feel it too.
まだまだぜんぶ足らないけど
There's still so much lacking, but—
ヒロインオーディション
Heroine audition—
選んでそしてワタシを
choose me and someday
いつかギュッとしてほしい
hold me tight.
ワタシなりのペースになるけど
It'll be at my own pace, but—
ヒロインオーディション
Heroine audition—
勇気をだしたらキミは
if I gather my courage, will you
「ねぇ、答えてくれるかな…？」
“Hey, give me an answer...?”
出会った一瞬ってかなり
The moment we met was quite
すごいミラクル
an amazing miracle.
このチャンスは赤い糸
This chance is a red thread of fate;
ギュッと手繰り寄せて
pulling it in tight,
運命にしよう
let's make it our destiny.
信じて…
Believing...
まっすぐ…
Straight ahead...
せーので言葉にして…！
Putting it into words on three...!
「キミのヒロインは誰…？」
“Who will be your heroine...?”
きっとキミの心を
I'm sure I'll make your heart
動かしてみせるよ
move and feel it too.
まだまだぜんぶ足らないけど
There's still so much lacking, but—
ヒロインオーディション
Heroine audition—
選んでそしてワタシを
choose me and someday
いつかギュッとしてほしい
hold me tight.
「ありがとう、ずっと大好きだよ！」
“Thank you, I've always loved you so much!”
ヒロインオーディション
Heroine audition—
選んでそしてワタシを
choose me and someday
いつかギュッとしてほしい
hold me tight.
「ありがとう、ずっと大好きだよ！」
“Thank you, I've always loved you so much!”
アキロゼさんの声とお歌が大好き♡アキロゼさんみたいなヒロインになれるようにがんばるBAUるね〜！！いつか二人で歌おうね!! BAU BAU!!
We love Aki-rose's voice and singing! We'll work hard to be heroines like her, BAU BAU!! Let's sing together someday!! BAU BAU!!
もういいじゃん ムキになっちゃって カッコつけて カッコよくない
Enough already, getting all worked up and putting on airs when you're not even cool.
そういうの嫌いになってんだ ほっといてよ 知りたくない
I've grown to hate stuff like that, just leave me alone, I don't want to know.
もういいじゃん けにになってんの 嫉妬したり じっとできない
Enough already, getting all weirdly obsessed, feeling jealous and unable to stay still.
聞こえないよ 耳塞いだっていって来るじゃん しんどいな
I can't hear you, even if I plug my ears you keep coming at me, it's so exhausting.
僕は誰も望まないよ
I don't wish for anyone else,
だから僕のことそっとしといて
so please just leave me be.
歌いだけのバカにハイハイハイ 受けるまたの腰待ってるねだとか
Just a singing idiot, high high high—waiting for your next turn, right?
本当は怯えてる 吠えるだけの弱虫だだだ
Truth is, I'm just a coward who only barks, scared out of my mind.
痛い癖に耐えてハイハイハイ いつも平気なフリばっかなの
Enduring even though it hurts, high high high—always pretending like everything's fine.
僕は壁を張ったまま笑う それ以上近づかないででで
I smile with a wall put up, so don't get any closer than this!
ばかばっか ばかばっか ばかばっか やだ ばかばっか
Idiots, idiots, idiots, no, idiots!
もういいじゃん まだ怒ってんの ほっといてよ ほっとできない
Enough already, are you still mad? Just leave me be—I can't just ignore it.
見ないように目をそらしたって ついてくるじゃん やっぱり
Even if I look away so I don't see, you still follow me after all.
転がったら起きればいいじゃん 失ったら探せばいいじゃん
If you fall over, just get back up; if you lose something, just search for it.
間違ったら直せばいいじゃん やんなくなったらやめればいいじゃん
If you make a mistake, fix it; if you're done doing it, just stop.
どんな大変なことがおきだって
No matter what terrible thing happens,
きみのあしのそのしたには
right beneath your feet,
とってもとってもじょうぶな「ばね」がついているんだぞ
there is a very sturdy spring attached!
おしつぶされそうな そんなときだって
Even in times when you feel like
ぐっ！とひざっこしょうにゆうきをためれ
you're being crushed, gather your courage,
「いまだ！スタンバイ！オーケー！」
"Now! Standby! OK!"
そのときをまつのみな
Wait for that moment.
おもいがらないいのになし
The wind is calling you.
いまこそ！ぼよよよ〜んとそらへ
Now is the time! Let's jump up high
とびあがってみよう ほらあのくもまで
into the sky, look, all the way to those clouds!
てがとどきそう
My hands feel like they can reach,
ぼよよよ〜んさいたかく とびこえてゆこう
boyoyoyo~n, high up, let's leap across!
ぼよよよ〜んとそらへ とびあがってみよう
Now is the time! Let's jump up high
ほら あのほしさえ てがとどきそう
into the sky, look, all the way to those stars!
ぼよよよ〜ん
My hands feel like they can reach,
たかくときこえてゆこう
boyoyoyo~n, high up, let's leap across!
ほしのしずくは はじめてのあしたへとつづく
The star's guide will lead us
ぼよよよ〜ん yeah〜
to our first tomorrow!
Boyoyoyo~n, yeah~
きゅーぴっと。
Kyuupiddo.
なんとなく声がソワソワ
A faint voice is ringing out,
ちょっと落ち着かないな
somewhat unsettling.
まだまだだって
It's still early,
いつからかそれがまぶしくなる
but since when did it become so dazzling?
気づいてないんない きっとあまいそんな言葉で yeah
You probably haven't noticed,
もう跳ねちゃって 捻を打っちゃって
Heart beating fast, hitting a nerve,
ねーって僕の口ばっかでね
it's always just my mouth talking.
だから今押し込んで 飲み込んで何か
So right now, let's swallow it all down,
おしくこころをばいして うずまく恋に浸して
twist our hearts, and pass the bitter pill!
もう君はサイテーだ
You're already out of bounds,
かなわないな
it's never going to happen!
きみのきゅーぴです むがちゅうちゅう きっとゆめにでてくる
Your Kyuupiddo's dream is spinning around,
ちゅちゅちゅちゅ ちゅちゅちゅちゅ
chuchuchu, chuchuchuchu!
きゅーきゅーです またむちゅちゅ ちょっとんだんでくる
Kyuu-kyuu, I want you even more now,
ちゅちゅちゅちゅ ちゅちゅちゅちゅ
chuchuchu, chuchuchuchu,
きゅっと抱きしめて
give me a tight hug!
どうしてらったったらったった
Why is that?
きみはまだ知らない事情
You still don't know the situation,
あたしもみえてないんでしょう
and I haven't seen it either, I bet.
なっちゃったなっちゃった
Oops, it slipped out!
あの子には見せちゃう美生
I'll show that girl my best side,
おもうだけで嫉妬しょう
feigning jealousy just out of mind.
あいだじゃそのまなざし
That look in your eyes,
さがしつづけた ほうせきみたい
I want to keep searching for those jewels!
でもまだ まだきずつくこと ピンチだ
But still, it hurts so much, it pinches!
うだするあたしも愛して
Love the clumsy me too,
こえづくじぶんを愛して
love the crying me too!
もうあたしサイテーだ
Oh, you're the absolute worst,
やめれないから
I just can't quit you!
きみのきゅーぴです またむちゅちゅ もっとほしくなってきた
Your Kyuupiddo's dream is spinning around,
ちゅちゅちゅちゅ ちゅちゅちゅちゅ
chuchuchu, chuchuchuchu!
ぎぶゆーらぶかんじょう りゅうりゅうずっときもちあふれる
I want all your love and emotion,
ちゅちゅちゅちゅ ちゅちゅちゅちゅ
chuchuchu, chuchuchuchu,
きゅっと抱きしめて
give me a tight hug!
ちゅちゅちゅちゅ ちゅちゅちゅちゅ
chuchuchu, chuchuchuchu,
きゅっと抱きしめて
give me a tight hug!
もうかくせないけど
I can't hide it anymore,
とまらないこどう
it's an unstoppable impulse!
ゆめからさまさて
Awakening from the dream,
きづいていま
I'm realizing it right now.
we'd run right through those nights
i'll never find my way back to you
We'd run right through those nights
I'll never find my way back to you inside this labyrinth of lights
there was madness in the meaning
never laughless, we were screaming
at the top of our lungs to the numbness, this city never died
I'll fly, no proof
those heights, I'll never find another chance to say, hey, thanks for saving my life
I was hopeless, it was stinging
running roadless
we were singing at the top of our lungs to the numbness, this city never died
What was the root of it all? I couldn't say.
Used to jump and then fall, rugged and clichéd.
Would shrug it off without complaint, not a sound
no use in trying to find friends 'cause in the end nobody sticks around
It's when you shoved yourself into a crowded place that you turned around and found yourself in love in outer space
cue the reckless nights, no strings, laughing at our own dreams, just what the hell was so funny?
Bark up the wrong tree, stumble, used to falling great heights amidst a concrete jungle, singing 'cause it felt right
We mixed the ennui and troubles, rhyming our discontent, and though it's history, I can't forget the time that we spent
Convinced that this could mean another end exists between real and pretend, a twisted alter-fiction where I missed my chance, did not ascend
and disappearing into the mist of never happened is the me that I can never befriend, and let it go
Fade in, fade out, this crazy dream, without a direction, floating aimlessly
there's nothing left back there for me
Breathe in, but it won't stop the rain from pouring
We'd run right through those nights
I'll never find my way back to you inside this labyrinth of lights
there was madness in the meaning, never laughless
we were screaming at the top of our lungs to the numbness, this city never died
But was there ever a soul inside? Chasing fireflies between the soaring high-rises, left a trail behind, defined it, wasted time of our lives.
Silent singer, overworked and underpaid, thinks an office is a coffin until off is where you're laid
yet a thought persists, an optimist who ought to be afraid, saw the "nothing wrong" in writing songs behind the lonely shade
Is the world a sadder place without the words that you conveyed when the ladder fell and shattered every bar that we had played?
Doesn't matter in the end the sound diminished and decayed, and your friends grew tired of fantasy, you're wishing they had stayed
you don't get to say "I miss you", you watched your heroes fade into the rear view mirror of the villain you portrayed
stop the pity party, listen, you don't get to be dismayed, you don't get to be emotional, feel blessed you got it made, these the best of years of life because you chose to make a trade, recollect the days you hoped and you prayed for this
What is there to miss?
Fade in, fade out, this hazy dream, without a direction, roaming aimlessly
there's nothing left back there for me
Pretend it's the end of a made-up story
I'll fly, no proof
those heights, I'll never find another chance to say, "Hey, thanks for saving my life."
I was hopeless, it was stinging
driving roadless
we were singing at the top of our lungs to the numbness, this city never died
I say goodbye to the soul inside, and yet somehow, there was romance in our self-hate, we've got no chance
in this light maze, but let's hold hands through the night haze, we'll run so fast
'til the school chime, 'til the train runs, we know it's time, we're the sane ones
waking up now, to the real life, let me daydream, till the next night
I'll keep waiting, I'll keep waiting for you
Waking up now, to my real life, let me daydream, till the next flight, drowning so long, I got older, now the crowd's gone, is it over? Is it over?
Waking up now, to my real life, let me daydream, till the next flight
running so long, I got older, now the crowd's gone
is it over? Is it over?
さあ 教えてよ 一途な恋のルールを♡
Come on, teach me the rules of faithful love ♡
女の子は マストだけなの？
Is being a girl all that matters?
もし万かがいざいません あなたの世界には
If by any chance there isn't anyone else in your world—
他の1人一番なんてあるはずないの
there's no way you'd have another number one!
誰もが羨むレベルで愛してよ
Love me on a level everyone would envy!
思わずマヒして見たくなるよな
So much that it makes me want to go numb,
恋しようね！ねぇ早くちゃける
let's fall in love! Hey, hurry up and—
涙々 一途ってトレンド トレンド
Tears, tears, faithful is the trend!
よっそ見しないでね ダーリン ダーリン時代遅れのの？
Don't look away, darling, darling, are you out of style?
Only Oneにしよ 好き好き いつだって私でしょ？
Let's make it Only One, love-love, it's always been me, right?
あなたはほら 最先端でいてよ♡
You, look, stay on the cutting edge ♡
じゃあ 教えてよ
Well then, teach me
あなたの頭の中
inside your head—
壊れそうな目も 私のものよ♡
even those eyes that look ready to break are mine ♡
少しの秘密も 2人にはありえないわ
Even the smallest secrets can't exist between us!
すべてを預けて 鍵しごとなんてないのよ
Entrust everything to me, there are no locked secrets!
ねぇ 気づいちゃってる 涙々
Hey, you've already noticed, tears, tears,
素直ってトレンド トレンド
honest is the trend, the trend!
秘密なんてない ダーリン ダーリン
There are no secrets, darling, darling,
まとはずれないのよ 正直にしよ
it's not off the mark, let's be honest!
好き好き 永遠に結びましょ
Love-love, let's be bound together forever!
あなたはほら 最先端でいてよ
You, look, stay on the cutting edge!
どんな時も 胸を震わせてね 離れてても
Make my heart tremble no matter what time, even if we're apart—
ほら あなたって そう あなたって
Look, you, yes, you—
こんなに素敵なの この世のこの世の終わりまで
how wonderful you are, until the end of this world!
神から神まで つなぎましょ 私の私の宝物
Let's connect from start to finish, my, my treasure!
そうでしょ？そう でしょ？ 恋しようよ
Right? Right? Let's fall in love!
ねぇ 流行っちゃってる 涙々
Hey, it's trending, tears, tears,
一途ってトレンド トレンド
faithful is the trend, the trend!
よっそ見しないでね ダーリン ダーリン
Don't look away, darling, darling,
時代遅れなの？ Only Oneにしよう
are you out of style? Let's make it Only One!
好き好き いつだって私でしょ？ あなたはほら
Love-love, it's always been me, right? You, look,
最先端でいてよ 私だけでいてよ♡
stay on the cutting edge, only be with me ♡
お願い お願い 私だけよ♡
Please, please, only me ♡
私だけいてよ♡
Only be with me ♡
What is? That was our brand new original song,
That was our brand new original song,
Ichizutte Trend! That was our original song,
Ichizutte Trend, desu! Don't you think it's a cute song?
"Ichizutte Trend"! Don't you think it's a cute song?
It was written and composed by the amazing
キヨシ竜次 さんです!
Ryuji Kiyoshi!
We're so so honored and cute!
作詩作曲は キヨシ竜次さんでした!
It was written and composed by Ryuji Kiyoshi!
そう、キヨシさんにオリジナル曲を書いていただけて光栄です!そう、夢でした!
Yes, we're so honored he wrote an original song for us! It was a dream!
And it's our loveiest, doviest song yet!
And it's our loveliest, dovie-duvviest song yet!
So you know, we hope you like it lots and lots!
And it will be released on digital streaming outlets at midnight today!
そう、この配信の後、0時からデジタルリリースされますので、いっぱい聴いてくれたら嬉しいです!
Yes, right after this stream, at midnight, it will have a digital release, so we'd be so happy if you listen to it a lot!
I was gonna be announced... oh those pretty zoy-zoy!
I was gonna make the announcement... oh, those were pretty big...
ねぇねぇ、
Hey, hey,
重大発表だったっけ？
Was there a major announcement?
あれ、What do you think, Ruffians?
Wait, what do you think, Ruffians?
はいっ！
Yes!
ノオー！ノオー！ノオー！ノオー！
No! No! No! No!
It's so exciting to have a new...
Wait, wait, wait, by us!
Not quite yet, we still have something, huh?
Did you want to take a look at it? Huh?
Do you want to know what the big announcement is?
Yea- Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
オッケー！オッケー！じゃあ、もこちゃん！
Okay! Okay! So, Moko-chan!
イエス、もこーかい！
Yes, Moko-kai!
オッケー！オッケー！
Okay! Okay!
Here we go, BAU BAUーー！！
Here we go, BAU BAU--!!
ふわふわ
Fuwa-fuwa
もこもこ
moko-moko
魔界乃番犬シスターズ☆★
Underworld Guard Dog Sisters☆★
この世界に爆誕“BAU”DOLです
Exploding into this world as a “BAU”DOL!
BAUBAU!!
めくるめくランデブー
Dizzying rendez-vous,
背中に君を感じたいの
I want to feel you on my back.
ふわふわ
Fuwa-fuwa
もこもこ
moko-moko
魔界乃番犬シスターズ☆★
Underworld Guard Dog Sisters☆★
この世界に爆誕“BAU”DOLです
Exploding into this world as a “BAU”DOL!
BAUBAU!!
私たち
We,
フワモコのファーストアルバムの発売が決定しました！
have decided to release FUWAMOCO's 1st album!
アルバムタイトルは「FUWAMOCO à la mode 〜いつだってあなたの笑顔を守るのっ〜」！
The album title is 'FUWAMOCO à la mode ~forever protecting your smile~'!
ジャケイラストは、イラストレーターの渡辺あきお先生！
The cover illustration is by illustrator Akio Watanabe-sensei!
フワモコの憧れの方に描いてもらえることになって、本当に嬉しいです！
We are so happy to have someone Fuwamoko admire draw it!
オー！
Oh!
現在制作中のイラストを特別に見せちゃいます！
We'll give you a special peek at the illustrations currently in production!
じゃーん！
Ta-da!
今回のアルバムは2枚組で作りました！
This album was made as a 2-disc set!
ディスク1の収録楽曲はなんと11曲！新曲もたくさんです！
Disc 1 features a whopping 11 songs, with lots of brand-new tracks!
ディスク2はアドヴェントのオリジナル曲のフワモコ歌唱バージョンと、アルバムについて語っているアフターパーティです！
Disc 2 features Fuwamoko's singing versions of Advent's original songs and an after-party talk about the album!
詳細はまだ内緒だから、続報を待っててね！
Details are still a secret, so stay tuned for further updates!
さらにさらに、アルバムにはCD以外のものもたくさん詰め込みました！
Furthermore, we've packed the album with plenty of items besides the CD!
キラキラステッカーシート、アクリルスタンド、ホロカ、アナザージャケット、そして2人で心を込めてラフィーアンズに向けて書いたお手紙！
A sparkly sticker sheet, acrylic stand, Holoca, another jacket, and a heartfelt letter written by the two of us for the Ruffians!
そしてそして、2人で頑張って買ってくれた皆さん全員に直筆サインをかくよ！
And what's more, we'll write hand-signed autographs for everyone who does their best to buy it!
私たちのファーストアルバム、たくさんの人が聞いてくれたら嬉しいな〜！
We'd be so happy if lots of people listen to our 1st album~!
Big huge news!
Our very first album is finally happening!
The title is 'FUWAMOCO à la mode ~forever protecting your smile~'.
The cover illustration is by Akio Watanabe-sensei.
An illustrator we've always looked up to!
We're so happy you agreed to draw for us.
Wow-wow!
And we want to show you something special right now, the illustration still in progress!
Ta-da!
This album is a two-disc set.
Disc 1 has 11 songs and so many brand-new ones!
Disc 2 is Fuwamoko's own vocal version of Advent's original songs, plus an after-party talking all about the album!
But you know, we can't spill any more details yet, so stay tuned!
Mmm.
And that's not all, the album is packed with more than just the CD.
A sparkly sticker sheet, acrylic stand, Holoca, an alternate jacket, and a letter that the two of us wrote from our hearts just for you!
And you know, the two of us are working hard to hand-sign every single copy for everyone who buys one!
We'd be so happy if lots of Ruffians get to listen to our first album!
Wow-wow!
Wow-wow! We're so happy!
It's finally happening! It's our 1st album! It's finally happening!
ずっと秘密にしてたフワモコのアルバムですよ！
It's Fuwamoko's album that we kept secret all this time!
すごい！CD、CD、CD！見て、見て、CD、アルバムゲット、手に入れよう、みんな！
Amazing! CD, CD, CD! Look, look, CD, get the album, let's get it everyone!
いや、これだ！これが私たちがいつも作ってる……
No, this is it! This is what we always make...
This means Moko-chan? Hold it in your paws!
Hold it in your paws! You can!
Yeah!
Thank you so much, Ruffians!
Thank you for always supporting us!
if I always stick to it, arigatou! Arigatou!
It's thanks to you, Ruffians, that we can do all of these amazing things!
本当にありがとう！
Thank you so much!
To repeat the important point, okay?
Pre-order start very soon!
Pre-order starts very soon!
9 PM JST or 5 AM PT, okay?
Yeah, right after this, okay? Right away!
待望の、今日は21時！
Today's reservations start at 21:00!
そう、このあとすぐ予約開始しちゃうよ！
Right after this, pre-orders start right away!
Are you ready?
Ready? Yeah!
And...
Did we mention? Every single CD will be signed by us!
Yeah, let's these boys! Yeah, and...
That's going to be signed with all our hearts!
All our hearts! The CD,
全部、この二人から直筆サインがありますよ！
All of them will have handwritten signatures from both of us!
いや、書きますよ！
Yeah, we'll write them!
心を込めて！
With all our hearts!
大事に作っているアルバムなので、みんなの手元に届いてほしいです！
We made this album with so much care, we want it to reach everyone!
Take complete, yeah!
But this album really means so much to us, so it'll mean so much to us if you could get a copy!
This album really means so much to us, so it means the world if you get a copy!
And listen to all precious songs that we put all of our hearts into all the moments all the time, okay?
And listen to all the precious songs we put our hearts into all the time!
You know, this is the day! The day we're giving up this entire year! Thank you!
You know, this is the day! The day we've been giving it our all this year!
And, wait, you know, it's not done here yet! No!
And wait, it's not done here yet! No!
We'll continue to work really hard on it, so it'll be everything that you'll dream of, okay?
We'll continue to work really hard, so it'll be everything you dream of!
Oh, thank you all for your...
You're excited? Yeah!
You excited? Yeah!
Yeah, please get it right after this, okay?
And don't forget Washington and Aidan now! Well, Wolfy!
With that, we'd like to continue to sing two final songs for you today!
And one of those songs is a Senpai's song who we really admire as an idol!
And one of those songs is a Senpai's song we really admire as an idol!
次の曲は、アイドルとしてとっても尊敬していた先輩の曲です！
The next song is by a Senpai we deeply respected as idols!
Wolfians, we hope our feelings reach you.
Please listen to Aqua-iro Palette!
何をしても不器用で
I'm so clumsy in everything that I do,
何かとミスしてばっか
Things go wrong 'cause I make mistakes a lot.
ダメダメな私だって できることがあるの
I feel so useless, but there is something I can do!
凹んで悲しくたって
When you are feeling blue and sad,
笑顔にしてあげるんだ
I can always make you smile!
ここにいるから 早く私を見つけてね
I'm right here, so please find me soon!
(love you love you. I love you.)
(love you love you. I love you so much.)
愛して もっと
Need you to love me more,
いつでも隣にいるし
I'll be by your side every time,
いつでも一緒に笑える
And we can always laugh together.
私をたくさん知って
Get to know me a lot more,
たくさん好きって言って
And tell me you love me so much!
ワガママで朝も苦手
Selfish and not a morning person,
ドジだしダメダメだけど
Clumsy and good for nothing, but...
それでも私のことを 見ててね
Still, please keep your eyes on me!
描く夢の未来へ続く 道をキミと歩けますように
I hope to walk the path of our future dreams with you!
ねぇ、もっと!
Hey, even more!
好きになってもらいたいのだって
I want you to fall in love with me!
(love you love you. I love you so much.)
頭の中は君ばっかっていうくせして
Acting like my head is only full of you!
鈍感だしダメダメだけどさ
I'm dense and hopeless, but still...
もうヤキモチしちゃうわ ah
I get so jealous, ah!
ずっとずっと好きがいの
Wanting your love forever and ever,
心の奥もときめいちゃうくらいに
Making my heart race deep inside!
こっち向いててねだりん?
Look this way, darling?
もう離さないから絶対に!
I'll never let you go, absolutely!
(love you love you. I love you.)
(love you love you. I love you so much.)
愛して もっと
Need you to love me more,
君が居るから私 いつでも頑張れるんだ
Because you're here, I can always try my best.
凹んで悲しくたって 君がいるから...
Even when I'm feeling blue and sad, because you're here...
君がいるから歩いて来れた 君が居なくちゃ前も見れない
I could walk this far because you're here, and I can't look ahead without you!
君がいるから 歩いてこれた
Because you are here, I was able to walk here
涙が出なくなっちゃうくらい
To the point where tears won't fall anymore
前も見えない
I can't even see ahead
嫌なこととか辛いこととか明日って
Bad things, painful things, tomorrow
君の力でここまで笑ってこれたんだ
I was able to smile up to here thanks to your strength
今度こそ私たちがぐっと引っ張って連れてくんだ!
This time, we'll pull you along and take you there!
君がいるから 私がいるの
Because you are here, I am here
こんな私を愛してくれて...
For loving someone like me...
ねぇもっと ねぇもっと まだもっと
Hey more, hey more, even more
受け止めてよね ねぇいいの? ねぇいい?
Accept me, hey is that okay? Hey okay?
さぁ声を上げて!
Come on, raise your voice!
ねぇもっと ねぇもっと 好きになってもらいたいの
Hey more, hey more, I want you to love me more
いつでもそう 私ばかり見せたいの
Always showing only me
そっぽなんて許さないわ ねぇほら夢中にしちゃうわ
I won't let you look away, hey look, I'll make you obsessed
ずっとずっと好きがいいの
I want you to love me forever and ever
心も体も触っちゃうくらいに
So much that you touch both heart and body
こっち向いててよ ダーリン もう離さないから
Look this way, darling, because I won't let go anymore
絶対に 絶対ね 絶対よ 約束だよ!
Definitely, definitely right, definitely a promise!
We love you so much! 大〜好き Ruffians!!
We love you so much! Da-suki Ruffians!
Love you love you!
I love you so much! Love you love you!
We'll continue to do our ALL to protect your smiles as BAUDOLS!
愛しちゃもっと!
Love me even more!
あまいろClearSky はじまりの歌
Amairo ClearSky, the song of beginnings
いつしか夢中につけてた 遠い夢
A distant dream I found myself immersed in
一人じゃ見えなかった景色
Scenery I couldn't see all by myself
涙 続く風の音 加速していく想いに
Tears, the sound of continuous wind, feelings accelerating
戸惑いを覚えた
I felt bewildered
ちょっと追いかけた理想の姿は
The ideal figure I briefly chased
まだ届かなくて遠いけど
Is still far and out of reach, but
きっとこの瞬間をかけがえないみんなで
Surely this irreplaceable moment with everyone
共に行くよ 手をつないで ずっと
We'll go together, hand in hand, always
輝き宿して 夢の場所へ
Holding radiance, to the place of dreams
駆け抜けていく 僕たちの青春の光は
Running through, the light of our youth
誰にも止められないよ 笑い合う分だけ優しく
Cannot be stopped by anyone, as kind as we share our smiles
こぼれる涙さえも
Even the spilling tears
ほら輝かせ 明日へ運ぶから 君の隣へ
Look, making them shine and carrying them to tomorrow, right beside you
僕たちは 世界を超えていく 迎えに行くよ
We will transcend the world and go greet you
まだ見えない明日も きらめきに変えてきっと
Even tomorrow which we cannot see yet, turning it into sparkle
僕たちが 未来へと 連れていくから
We will lead you toward the future
背伸びしては手を伸ばす 憧れの
Stretching up and reaching out, our longing
行き先示す星になろう
Let's become the star that shows the way
つまづくその度に 手を差し伸べ合えたら
Every time we stumble, if we reach out our hands to each other
すぐに届くはずさ
We'll surely reach it soon
そっと心とした 小さな勇気が
Gently joining our small courages
もう消えないように繋げよ
Connecting them so they won't fade away
不安も愛しさも 大切に抱きしめて
Embracing both anxiety and affection dearly
共に行くよ 目を合わせて
We'll go together, meeting eyes
舞い散る希望へ 飛び出せるよ
To the scattering hopes, we can burst out
突き抜けていく 僕たちの透き通る決意は
Breaking through, our clear-cut determination
まだまだ止められないよ
Still cannot be stopped
歩き足りない今日こそ ときめきに変えてもっと
Today, which we haven't walked enough of, turning it into excitement
僕たちが いつまでも 背中を押すから
Because we will push your back forever
Wafuu! Hey, we have something we want to share with you.
It's now been 3 years since we made our debut here in hololive.
There's been so many precious memories made, laughed together,
and even some tears, they were precious too.
It's been lots of challenges, but it's all been worth it.
The attitude with dreams we dreamt 3 years ago have been coming true one by one.
And now, our dreams have become our own first live! But our albums coming true too.
Yeah, and my soul is kind of like thankful.
We want to continue on this journey, no matter what comes our way,
as long as we're together, we know that we can do the impossible.
Thank you for being our precious Ruffians, here by our side.
We'll continue to protect your smile forever and ever! Bau Bau!
ずっと一人で描いてた
I'd been drawing it all alone,
いつか誰かがこんな人になって
hoping someday someone would become like this.
少しずつ芽生える大好きを紡ぎ どこまでも熱く
Spinning the growing love little by little, burning endlessly,
明日色の空へ駆け抜けていく
running through toward the sky the color of tomorrow.
僕たちの青春の光は
The light of our youth
誰にも止められないよ
can't be stopped by anyone!
笑い合う分だけ優しく こぼれる涙さえほら
As gentle as we laugh together, even the spilled tears, look,
輝かせて明日へ運ぶから
will shine and carry us to tomorrow.
君の隣へ 僕たちは
By your side, we
世界を超えていく 迎えに行くよ
will cross the world, going to greet you!
まだ見えない明日日も きらめきに変えてきっと
Even tomorrow we can't see yet, turning it into sparkle, surely
僕たちが未来へと
we will take you
果てのない未来へと 連れていくから
to a boundless future!
We're together! FURR-EVER!! It's all thanks to hololive